Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Athletics Department web crawls, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011; Tufts University; 40 Web sites
  - Directions to Tufts University Athletics Facilities, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00007; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Athletics Intramurals, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00008; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Department of Sports Medicine, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00009; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Athletics Staff Directory, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00010; Department of Athletics
  - Visitor's Guide, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00011; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Baseball, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00012; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Field Hockey, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00013; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Golf, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00014; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Basketball, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00015; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Crew, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00016; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Ice Hockey, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00017; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Lacrosse, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00018; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Soccer, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00019; Department of Athletics
  - Tufts University Men's Squash, 2012 -- 2022; UA046.011.00020; Department of Athletics
- Additional accessions, circa 1950 -- 2012; UA046.012
  - Tufts Cavalcade of Champions, 1980; UA046-001
  - Cousens Gymnasium Renovation Pictures, 2003 -- 2009; UA046-006
  - Jumbo footprints, 2009-05; UA046-009
  - Swim team digital files and photos, 1999 -- 2012; UA046-040
    From Nancy Bigelow
  - Donald Cooney and Tufts vs. U.N.H posters, 1950; UA046-047 (Box Small Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Tufts vs. Bowdoin NCAA Finals, 2008-11-23; UA046-048
    This is a video of 2008 NCAA Field Hockey Championships, Tufts vs. Bowdoin.
  - Tufts Track photographs, 2002 -- 2003; UA046-049
    This digital object contains 179 photographs from Tufts Track.
  - Tufts Track photographs, 2005-01-15; UA046-050
    This digital object contains 213 photographs from Tufts Track.
  - Men's Soccer photographs, 2004; UA046-051
    This digital object contains 36 photographs from men's soccer.
  - Tufts Men's Soccer photographs, 2004-09-22; UA046-052
    This digital object contains 138 photographs from men's soccer.
  - Tufts Field Hockey photographs, 2005-09-17; UA046-053
    This digital object contains 156 photographs from Tufts Field Hockey.
  - Tufts Womens Basketball photographs, 2003-01-28; UA046-054
    This digital object contains 359 photographs and 8 contact sheets from Tufts Womens basketball.
  - Athletics Winter Action Photos Women's Basketball vs Emmanuel, 2006-01-10; UA046-055
    This digital objects contains approximately 230 photographs from a Women's Basketball game vs Emmanuel College.
  - Tufts Womens Basketball photographs, 2005-01-08; UA046-056
    This digital object contains 137 photographs from Tufts Womens Basketball.
  - Tufts Cross Country photographs, 2002-10-11; UA046-057
    This digital object contains 56 photographs and 3 contact sheets.
  - Tufts Cross Country photographs, 2004-10-08; UA046-058
  - Men's Lacrosse photographs, 2011; UA046-059
    This digital object contains 91 individual and team photographs of the Tufts Men's Lacrosse team.
  - Middlebury photographs, 2010-05-09; UA046-060
    This digital object contains 137 photographs from the 2010 NESCAC (New England Small College Athletic Conference) Men's Lacrosse Champsionship game against Middlebury College. Tufts won the game by a score of 13-12.
  - Men's Lacrosse WNEC vs. Tufts photographs, 2003-03-19; UA046-061
    This digital object contains photographs of a Men's Lacrosse game vs. WNEC that was played at Springfield College.
  - Tufts Men's Lax photographs, 2004-04-07; UA046-062
    This digital object contains 259 photographs from Tufts Men's Lacrosse.
  - Tufts Daily Lacrosse Project Final Selections, 2005; UA046-063
    This digital object contains photographs from Tufts Men's Lacrosse.
  - Tufts Daily Lacrosse Project Stock Photos, 2005; UA046-064
  - Tufts Womens Tennis photographs, 2003-04-15; UA046-065
    This digital object contains 241 photographs and 10 contact sheets from Tufts Womens Tennis.
  - FB Individual photographs, 2005; UA046-066
    This digital object contains photographs of individual Tufts Football players.
  - Tufts Football Team Photos, 2005-09-10; UA046-067
    This digital object contains 67 photographs of Tufts Football.
  - Tufts Spring Photos, 2006; UA046-068
    This digital object contains 7 photographs from Tufts Spring Sports, including Women's and Men's Lacrosse, Baseball, Softball, Women's and Men's Tennis, and Sailing.
  - Tufts Winter Teams, 2006 -- 2007; UA046-069
    This digital object contains 7 photographs from Tufts Winter Sports teams, including: Women's and Men's Squash, Women's and Men's Basketball, Women's and Men's Swimming and Diving, and Hockey.
  - Winter Sports for Paul, 2006-02-22; UA046-070
    This digital object contains photographs from Basketball, Hockey, and Swimming.
  - Team Sports for Paul, 2005; UA046-071
    This digital object contains team photographs from Sailing and Men's Soccer.
  - Tufts photographs Men's and Women's Squash, 2006; UA046-072
    This digital object contains photographs from Men's and Women's Squash.
  - Team Photos Joanie Tobin, 2005; UA046-073
    This digital object contains photographs from Volleyball, Women's Soccer, Field Hockey, and Men's Cross Country.
  - Tufts FB photographs, 2006; UA046-074
    This digital object contains photographs of Tufts Football.
  - Tufts Mens Basketball photographs, 2004-02-03; UA046-075
    This digital object contains photographs from Tufts Mens Basketball.
  - Tufts Fall Team Photos, 2006; UA046-076
    This digital object contains team photographs for: Field Hockey, Men's Soccer (JV and Varsity), Women's Soccer, Women's Cross Country, Men's Cross Country, Volleyball, and Football.
  - Tufts Volleyball, 2003-10-21; UA046-077
    This digital object contains photographs from Tufts Volleyball.
  - Tufts Men's Hockey, 2005-01-25; UA046-078
    This digital object contains photographs from Men's Hockey.
  - Tufts University Baseball, 2007; UA046-079
    This digital object contains photographs from Tufts University Baseball. Materials copyrighted by Tim Morse, tim@morsephotography.com.
  - Athletics Winter Action Photos Ice Hockey vs. Wesleyan, 2006-02-03; UA046-080
    This digital object contains photographs of a Tufts vs. Wesleyan Ice Hockey game.
  - Tufts Men's Hockey photographs, 2003-01-31; UA046-081
    This digital object contains 250 photographs and 10 contact sheets of Tufts Men's Hockey.
  - Road to the Championship - Tufts Lacrosse National Champions DVD, 2010; UA046-082 (Case 82)
    A Film by Arlin Ladue.
  - Jumbo Footprints 1900-1950, Christina Szoke plus bibliography, 2000; UA046-083
    Contents of 3.5" floppy disk labelled "1. Footprints 1900-1950 Christina Szoke plus bibliography"
  - Tufts Footprints 1889-1900, Lisa McNally, 2001; UA046-084
    Contents of 3.5" floppy disk labelled "2. Tufts Footprints 1889-1900 Lisa McNally"
  - Footprints Table of Contents and additional notes, 2002-01-02; UA046-085
    Contents of 3.5" floppy disk labelled "3. Footprints Table of Contents 01-02-02. Addt'l notes. Janks[?] - typed - IA"
  - Tufts Men's Hockey photos and posters, 1960 -- 2000; UA046-086 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 10)
- 2017 accessions, 1982 -- 2002; UA046.013; 18 Linear Feet 15 record cartons
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  Transferred by staff and student workers in the Athletics Department on behalf of Branwen Smith King (women's track and cross country coach, 1982-2000), 2017, accession UA-2018-004.
  This series is arranged in received order. Box titles provided by Athletics department.
  This series contains women's cross country and outdoor and indoor track records kept by Branwen Smith King, women's track and cross country coach from 1982-2000. These records include rosters, results from meets, photographs, newsclippings, drills and exercises, schedules, programs, and athlete information. This series also contains one box of Branwen Smith King's files as part of the Athletics Department, including courses taught and other department business. Box titles provided by Athletics department.
  - Cross country, outdoor and indoor track and field binders, 1982 -- 1986; UA046.013.201; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 201)
    Student records are restricted 75 years from date of creation. This box may require review before it is available for use.
  - Cross country, outdoor and indoor track and field binders, 1986 -- 1989; UA046.013.202; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 202)
  - Cross country, outdoor and indoor track and field binders, 1990 -- 1993; UA046.013.203; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 203)
  - Cross country and track meets, 1998 -- 1999; UA046.013.204; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 204)
  - Cross country and track results, 1982 -- 2000; UA046.013.205; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 205)
  - Cross country and track meets and results, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.013.206; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 206)
  - Cross country and track meets and results, 1990 -- 1991; UA046.013.207; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 207)
  - Cross country and track meets and results, 1991 -- 1993; UA046.013.208; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 208)
  - Cross country and track meets and results, 1993 -- 1994; UA046.013.209; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 209)
  - Outdoor track and field, 1994 -- 1995; UA046.013.210; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 210)
  - Cross country and indoor track, 1995 -- 1996; UA046.013.211; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 211)
  - Cross country and outdoor track, 1995 -- 2000; UA046.013.212; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 212)
  - Cross country and track meets, 1999 -- 2001; UA046.013.213; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 213)
  - Misc. track and field results, circa 1998 -- 2000; UA046.013.214; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 214)
  - Branwen Smith King files, circa 1982 -- 2002; UA046.013.215; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 215)